Guide to the Francis Warrington Dawson Family Papers, 1386-1963, bulk 1859-1950 RL.10147
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1859-1963 and undated
  - Hayes, Chester to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 14)
  - Hayes, Elizabeth to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1936 (Box 14)
  - Hayward, D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1932 (Box 14)
  - Hazzard, E. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 14)
  - Hazzard, Miles to Dawson, F. W., 1885 (Box 14)
  - Hearn, E. L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1919-1920 (Box 14)
  - Hedeman, Jules to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 14)
  - Heim, [?] to [?], 1931-1932 (Box 14)
  - Heingarter, R. W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 14)
  - Heinzin, Ralph to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Helleisen-Périn, [?] to [?], 1932 (Box 14)
  - Helmbold, Elmo to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Hélouis, R. to [?], 1930-1931 (Box 14)
  - Hemphine, J. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 14)
  - Hennig, Helen to Barry, Stuyvesant, 1931 (Box 14)
  - Henriot, Emile to Dawson, Warrington, 1951-1952 (Box 14)
  - Hepbarn, Elizabeth to Dawson, Warrington, 1926 (Box 14)
  - Herbette, Maurice to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 14)
  - Herbetty, Jean to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 14)
  - Herbine, Charlotte to Dawson, Warrington, 1928 (Box 14)
  - Herbst, Charlie to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 15)
  - Herrick, Myron to Monsieur l'Abbé, 1928 (Box 15)
  - Herrick, Myron to Dawson, Warrington, 1923-1929 (Box 15)
  - Heyman, Katherine to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 15)
  - Heywood, C. P. to Lord Plymouth, 1914 (Box 15)
  - Hiatt, Walter to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 15)
  - Hiden, Cordelia to Morgan, Sarah, 1864 (Box 15)
  - Hill, Caroline to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 15)
  - Hill, John W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Hill, Lillian to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1933 (Box 15)
  - Hill, William to [?], 1888 (Box 15)
  - Hillman, James to various, 1931-1932 (Box 15)
  - Hills, L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 15)
  - Hippeau, Jean-Paul to [?], 1946 (Box 15)
  - Hise, W. D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1918 (Box 15)
  - Hitt, Russell to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Hochart, H. W. to various, 1930-1932 (Box 15)
  - Hocker, C. E. to [?], 1933 (Box 15)
  - Hoffman, Eleanor to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 15)
  - Hogon, Mattie to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Holland, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1912-1913 (Box 15)
  - Holland, H. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 15)
  - Hollings & Dothage to Morgan, Sarah, 1891 (Box 15)
  - Hollings, Frank to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Hollister, Paul to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 15)
  - Holmes, Henry to Morgan, James, 1889-1890 (Box 15)
  - Holmes, W. J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Hooper, Franklin to Dawson, Warrington, 1913 (Box 15)
  - Hopkins, J. T. to Dawson, Warrington, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Hopper, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1913 (Box 15)
  - Houdé, G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 15)
  - Houston, Alexander to Dawson, Warrington, 1917-1920 (Box 15)
  - Houston, Nora to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 15)
  - Howard, Roy to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1930 (Box 15)
  - Howe, Annie to Dawson, Warrington, 1913-1914 and undated (Box 15)
  - Howell, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Hrones, J. G. to [?], 1929 (Box 15)
  - Hue, Edmond to [?], 1932 (Box 15)
  - Huelsbeck, Clara to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 15)
  - Hufham, J. D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Huger, F. B. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1933 (Box 15)
  - Hughes, Charles to various, 1921 (Box 15)
  - Huidekoper, Frederic to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 15)
  - Hull, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Hull, [?] to [?], 1934 (Box 15)
  - Hume, Joseph to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 15)
  - Humphries, Bruce to Barry, Herbert, 1928 (Box 15)
  - Hunt, Henry to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 15)
  - Hunt, Henry to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 15)
  - Huntington, Douglas to Millerand, 1918 (Box 15)
  - Huntington, W. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 15)
  - Hutchinson, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 15)
  - Hutterly, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 15)
  - Hyde, A. R. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Hyde, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1947 and undated (Box 15)
  - Ide, John Jay to Dawson, Warrington, 1935-1939 (Box 15)
  - Ingram, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1932 (Box 15)
  - Institute of American Geneaology to members, 1932 (Box 15)
  - Izlar & Glaze to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 15)
  - Jackman, Reva to various, 1930 (Box 15)
  - Jackson, Margaret to Dawson, Warrington, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Jacobs, William to Dawson, F. W., 1889 (Box 15)
  - James T. White & Co. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 15)
  - James, Jules to Dawson, Warrington, 1925-1929 (Box 15)
  - Jamison, Atha to Dawson, F. W., 1889 (Box 15)
  - Jeffrey, H. T. (Mrs.) to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 15)
  - Jennison, J. Morgan to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 15)
  - Jervey, Theo to Dawson, Warrington, 1924-1936 (Box 15)
  - Jewett, Rutger to Gough, John, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Joffre, Henriette to Dawson, Warrington, 1920-1946; 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Bradley T. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Hallet to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1927 (Box 15)
  - Johnson, Nelson to Dawson, Warrington, 1928 (Box 15)
  - Johnson, S. to Dawson, Warrinton, 1931 (Box 15)
  - Johnston, Dawson to Dawson, Warrington, 1922-1925 (Box 15)
  - Johnston, Francis to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Johnston, George to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 15)
  - Johnston, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 15)
  - Johnstone, Margaret to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1935 (Box 15)
  - Joly, A. J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1948-1950 (Box 15)
  - Jones, B. B. to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1910 (Box 15)
  - Jones, Iona to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 15)
  - Jones, Willie to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 15)
  - Jouve, Jeanne to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Jouveau-Dubrevif, G. to [?], 1932 (Box 15)
  - Jusserand, J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1927 (Box 15)
  - Kain, F. B. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1931 (Box 15)
  - Karpinald, Louis to Swem, E. G., 1930 (Box 16)
  - Kaufman, A. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 16)
  - Kaufman, A. C. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 16)
  - Kaye, S. A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1946 (Box 16)
  - Kearney, [?] to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Keena, Eleanor to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 16)
  - Keena, L. J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 16)
  - Kellog, Frank to [?], 1928 (Box 16)
  - Kelly, William to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 16)
  - Kemp & Battle to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 16)
  - Kemper, D. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 16)
  - Kennedy, Hoffman to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 16)
  - Keogh, Will to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 16)
  - Kerkelly, Gabriel to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 16)
  - Kerney, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1918 (Box 16)
  - Keyes, George to various, 1954 (Box 16)
  - Khoury, G. T. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 16)
  - Kiernan, [?] to Weisenberg, Lee, 1930 (Box 16)
  - Kinard, J. P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Kincaid, Warren to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1933 (Box 16)
  - King, Grace to Dawson, Warrington, 1903-1930; 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Kipling, Carrie to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 16)
  - Kipling, Rudyard to Dawson, Warrington, 1917-1933 and undated (Box 16)
  - Kite, Elizabeth to various, 1931-1933 (Box 16)
  - Klumpke, Anna to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 16)
  - Knaff, F. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 16)
  - Knecht, Marcel to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1931 (Box 16)
  - Koenig, Andre to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 16)
  - Krans, H. S. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Labbé, J. to [?], 1932 (Box 16)
  - Labouchère, Elaine to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 16)
  - Lacabe, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1914-1916 (Box 16)
  - Laché, Jeanne to [?], 1922 (Box 16)
  - Lache, J. de to Dawson, Warrington, 1927 (Box 16)
  - Laemmle, Carl to Dawon, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Lafargue, André to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 16)
  - Lafargue, André to [?], undated (Box 16)
  - La Fleur, Abel to [?], 1918 (Box 16)
  - La Gorce, John to [?], undated (Box 16)
  - Lahm, F. P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 16)
  - Lambert-Blitz to Dawson, Warrington, 1938 (Box 16)
  - Lamkin, L. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 16)
  - Lamotte, Frances to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Landers, H. L. to Goodwin, W. A. R., 1931 (Box 16)
  - Landin, Harold to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 16)
  - Landowski, L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1948 (Box 16)
  - Landowski, Paul to Dawson, Warrington, 1951 (Box 16)
  - Lane, J. E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1932 (Box 16)
  - Laneroy, G. to Dawson, Warrington and [?], 1932 (Box 16)
  - Lange, Beatrice to Dawson, Warrington, 1909 (Box 16)
  - Langelaan, G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1932 (Box 16)
  - Langfier, Adolphe to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Langton, Arthur to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Lansing, Emma to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1939 and undated (Box 16)
  - Lansing, Katherine to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 (Box 16)
  - Lansing, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 16)
  - Larner, Robb to Dawson, F. W., 1886 (Box 16)
  - Larrabe, harold to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1934 (Box 16)
  - Lathan, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Lattre, Roger de to Dawson, Warrington, 1936 (Box 16)
  - Laury, Dorothy to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 16)
  - Lavagere, G. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 16)
  - Lavigerie, R. de to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 16)
  - Lawrence, Alberta to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 16)
  - Le Breton, D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 16)
  - Le Breton, Pauline to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 16)
  - Leclercy, Georges to Dawson, Warrington and [?], 1931-1933 (Box 16)
  - Lecomte, Georges to [?], 1953 and undated (Box 16)
  - Ledoux, C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 16)
  - Lee, C. to various, 1888 (Box 16)
  - Lee, Fitzhugh to Dawson, F. W., 1865-1883 (Box 16)
  - Lee, Fitzhugh to Morgan, Sarah, 1890 (Box 16)
  - Lefaivre, Jules to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 17)
  - Lefaivre, Jules to [?], 1927-1932 (Box 17)
  - Leffingnell, Alsop to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 17)
  - Legres, Genevieve to Dawson, Warrington, 1935 (Box 17)
  - Leharpe, A. Dormoy de to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1935 (Box 17)
  - Leland, Waldo to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 17)
  - Lemare, Paul to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 17)
  - LeRoy, Alexandre to Dawson, Warrington, 1912? (Box 17)
  - Leslie, C. P. to Dawson, F. W., 1871 (Box 17)
  - Letellier, Maurice to Dawson, Warrington, 1928-1932 (Box 17)
  - Letellier, Maurice to [?], 1930-1931 (Box 17)
  - Le Vasseur, A. to [?], 1932 (Box 17)
  - Light, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 17)
  - Linthicum, J. Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 17)
  - Litvinne, Félia to Dawson, Warrington, 1930-1934 and undated (Box 17)
  - Lodge, H. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1924 (Box 17)
  - Loeb, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1924 (Box 17)
  - Logan, Samuel F. to Dawson, Warrington, 1946-1948 (Box 17)
  - Lohrman, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1927 (Box 17)
  - Lomier, E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 17)
  - London, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 17)
  - Long, [?] to [?], 1934 (Box 17)
  - Louveau, Henriette to [?], 1934 and undated (Box 17)
  - Lowrie, W. L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Loys, Vincent de to [?], 1938 (Box 17)
  - Lukens, Henry to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 17)
  - Lupton, Stuart to Dawson, Warrington, 1927 (Box 17)
  - Lusher, A. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 17)
  - Lussy, A. de to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 17)
  - Lyon, Frederick to Dawson, Warrington, 1953 (Box 17)
  - Lyons, Loretta to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 17)
  - L'Youmayo, Le Roy to Northop, L. C., 1879 (Box 17)
  - Lytton, Neville to Dawson, Warrington, 1929 (Box 17)
  - Macbeth, Eliza to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 17)
  - MacDowall, H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1919-1920 (Box 17)
  - Mackey, E. W. M. to [?], 1879 and undated (Box 17)
  - Mackintosh, Walter to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - MacNaughten, Edgar to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Macrae, John to Barry, Herbert, 1909 (Box 17)
  - Maggs Brothers to Dawson, Warringon, 1932 (Box 17)
  - Magnus, R. to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 17)
  - Magrath, W. to Dawson, F. W. and [?], 1878 and undated (Box 17)
  - Maire de Versailles to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 17)
  - Malott, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Manalt, M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 17)
  - Manguin, S. to [?], 1931-1933 (Box 17)
  - Manigault, Robert to [?], 1931 (Box 17)
  - Mann, John to Morgan, Sarah, 1898 (Box 17)
  - Manning, Colin to Dawson, F. W., 1889 (Box 17)
  - Manning, Peyton to Dawson, F. W., 1865 (Box 17)
  - Mansuy, Madame to [?], 1920 (Box 17)
  - Marbeau, L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Marchesi, [B?] to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 17)
  - Marcou, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1914 (Box 17)
  - Mardière, F. de la to [?], 1932-1933 (Box 17)
  - Marignan, Robert to [?], 1932-1945 (Box 17)
  - Marion, Mérese to [?], 1931-1932 and undated (Box 17)
  - Marison, Fiscar to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 17)
  - Maris-Wilson, Edith to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 17)
  - Marmon, Marie-Louise de to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 17)
  - Marriner, Theodore to various, 1933-1934 (Box 17)
  - Marshall, Hattie to Dawson, Warrington, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Marshall, R. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 17)
  - Marot, André to [?], 1932 (Box 17)
  - Martellière, E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1948 (Box 17)
  - Martet, Jean to [?], 1917 (Box 17)
  - Martin, G. W. L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Martin, H. C. to [?], 1889 (Box 17)
  - Martin, Louis to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 17)
  - Mason, J. W. T. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1927 (Box 17)
  - Mason, Solila to [?], 1911 (Box 17)
  - Mason, W. R. to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1927 (Box 17)
  - Mather, Helen to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 17)
  - Mathot, A. L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1913 (Box 17)
  - Maurer, M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 17)
  - Maurice, Margot to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 (Box 17)
  - May, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1919-1922 (Box 17)
  - McAlpin, L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1912 (Box 17)
  - McClure, S. S. to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 17)
  - McCord, David to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - McCormick, Vance to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 17)
  - McDonald, M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - McElree, John to Dawson, F. W., 1887 and undated (Box 17)
  - McFadden, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1918 (Box 17)
  - McGahey, Sarah to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 17)
  - McIver, George to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 17)
  - McKinley, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 17)
  - McKissick, A. Foster to Morgan, Sarah, 1897 (Box 17)
  - McManaway, Maggie to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 17)
  - McMillan, Annie to Dawson, Warrington, 1913 (Box 17)
  - McOsker, J. A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1921-1922 (Box 17)
  - Meeks, Everett to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 18)
  - Meffre, Jacques to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 18)
  - Mehrmann, Maurice to Dawson, Warrington, 1921 (Box 18)
  - Meldrim, F. W. to Dawson, F. W., 1880s (Box 18)
  - Méline, J. to [?], 1904-1909 (Box 18)
  - Memminger, Lucien to Armour, Norman, 1930 (Box 18)
  - Mérelle, René to [?], 1932-1933 (Box 18)
  - Meriwether, R. L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1946 (Box 18)
  - Merlet, Janine to [?], 1933 (Box 18)
  - Merrien, P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 18)
  - Merrill, Theodore to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1935 and undated (Box 18)
  - Metcalf, Frank to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 18)
  - Meyer, Arthur to [?], undated (Box 18)
  - Meyer, Pierre to Dawson, Warrington, 1938 (Box 18)
  - Middleton, B. F. to Cocke, Jack, 1930 (Box 18)
  - Middleton, B. F. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 18)
  - Miehling, Elsa to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 18)
  - Miles, Eliza to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 18)
  - Miles, Richardson to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 18)
  - Miles, W. to [?], 1884 (Box 18)
  - Miller, C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1911-1931 (Box 18)
  - Miller, Newman to Dawson, Warrington, 1915 (Box 18)
  - Miller, R. to Morgan, Sarah, undated (Box 18)
  - Millet, Geraldine to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 18)
  - Millet, T. to [?], 1900 (Box 18)
  - Milligan, William to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 18)
  - Millward, J. to Dawson, Warringon, 1931-1933 (Box 18)
  - Minnigerode, C. Powell to Dawson, Warrington, 1924 (Box 18)
  - Miollis, Raymond to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 18)
  - Mitchell, B. to Barry, Stuyvesant, 1930 (Box 18)
  - Mitchell, Broadus to Barry, Ethel, 1930 (Box 18)
  - Mitchell, Caroline to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 18)
  - Mitchell, Cécile to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 18)
  - Mitchell, E. G. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 18)
  - Mitchell, Julian to Barry, Herbert, 1926 (Box 18)
  - Mitchell, W. E. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 18)
  - Monaghan, Frank to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1934 (Box 18)
  - Mondeley, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, 1907-1908 (Box 18)
  - Monnier, P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 18)
  - Monod, François to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 18)
  - Monod, François to [?], 1931-1932 (Box 18)
  - Montarnal, J. de to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 18)
  - Montjamont, T. de to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 and undated (Box 18)
  - Montozon-Brachet, René de to [?], 1930 (Box 18)
  - Moore, E. E. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 18)
  - Moore, James to [?], 1932 (Box 18)
  - Mordecai, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 18)
  - Moreno, Daniel to Dawson, Warrington, 1940 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Harjes, & Co. to Dawson, Warrington, 1925 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Helen to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 7)
  - Morgan, A. S. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889-1902 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Anne to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, B. L. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, E. M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1926 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Florence to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, George M. to various, 1859-1864 and undated (Box 18)
  - Morgan, George W. to Dawson, Warrington, 1882 (Box 18)
    It is written to F.W. Dawson, but written in FWD's hand, on N & C stationery. However, it is signed by James M Morgan, so it is technically from him. It is a legal document re: JMM's daughter.
  - Morgan, George W. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889-1892 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, H. W. to mother, 1860 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Helen to Morgan, Sarah, 1895-1897 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Howell with Morgan, Sarah, 1880-1908 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Howell to Dawson, Warrington, 1909-1946 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, J. M. M. to Dawson, F. W., 1874 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, J. M. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910-1925 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, John Hill to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Lillie to Jim and [?], 1863-1867 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, P. to Dawson, F. W., 1874 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, P. H. to Morgan Sarah and/or Dawson, Warrington, 1889-1899 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Sarah with Dunkin, Eunice, 1889-1903 (Box 18)
  - Morgan, Sarah to Dunkin, Eunice, 1904-1909; 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Morgan, Sarah to Lydia, 1872-1901 (Box 19)
  - Morgan, Sarah to Miriam, 1879 (Box 19)
  - Morgan, Sarah to various, 1873-1909 and undated; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Morgan, Thomas Gibbes to son, 1861-1862 (Box 19)
  - Morison, H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 19)
  - Moroes, J. A. to various, 1889 (Box 19)
  - Moroso, H. J. to Dawson, F. W., undated (Box 19)
  - Morrison, Rose to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 19)
  - Morse, Alex to Drum, Lavinia Morgan, 1889 (Box 19)
  - Morse, M. B. to Drum, Lavinia, 1889 (Box 19)
  - Morse, M. B. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 19)
  - Mott, Bentley to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 19)
  - Moulton, Louise to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 19)
  - Moutelles, L. de to [?], 1913 (Box 19)
  - Mumford, Edward to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Mun, A. to various, 1912 (Box 19)
  - Murat, Lucien to Dawson, Warrington, undated (Box 19)
  - Murdock, Henrietta to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 19)
  - Murphy, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1937 (Box 19)
  - Murray, Frank to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 19)
  - Murrin, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1934 (Box 19)
  - Muse, Benjamin to Dawson, Warrington, 1925-1927 (Box 19)
  - Musser, Mary to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Nac Veagh, John to various, 1930-1933 (Box 19)
  - Neave, H. E. to various, 1928-1932 (Box 19)
  - Nepveu, Edward to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1932 (Box 19)
  - Newell, Ella to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Newton, H. H. to Dawson, F. W., 1884 (Box 19)
  - Nolan, D. E. to Dawson, Warrington, 1939 (Box 19)
  - Nolan, J. Bennett to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Nolhac, Pierre to [?], 1926 and undated (Box 19)
  - Nordau, Anne to Dawson, Warrington, 1935-1952 (Box 19)
  - Nordau, D. M. to [?], 1907-1912 (Box 19)
  - Normand, H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 19)
  - Normandy, Georges to Dawson, Warrington, 1929-1931 (Box 19)
  - Normon, A. C. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Norris, C. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 19)
  - Northrop, A. P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1911-1927 (Box 19)
  - Northrop, L. C. to Dawson, F. W., 1879 and undated (Box 19)
  - Northrop, L. C. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 19)
  - Norhrop, W. B. to Dawson, Warrington, 1910 (Box 19)
  - Norton, Lawrence to Dawson, Warrington, 1922 (Box 19)
  - Norton, Theodore to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Nousset, L. to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 (Box 19)
  - Noyes, Elise to Dawson, Warrington, 1914-1921 and undated (Box 19)
  - Nussac, Louis de to [?], 1931 (Box 19)
  - Nussbaum, [?] to [?], 1931 (Box 19)
  - Ober, Harold to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 19)
  - O'Driscoll, D. M. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 19)
  - Ord, James to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 19)
  - Olghadjan, Charles to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Packer, John to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 19)
  - Paddock, Gordon to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 19)
  - Page, Richard du to [?], 1930-1935 (Box 19)
  - Page, Walter to Dawson, Warrington, 1913-1914 (Box 19)
  - Painleve, Paul to [?], 1933 (Box 19)
  - Palmer, E. H. to Dawson, Warrington, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Palmer, Florence to Dawson, Warrington, 1926-1939 (Box 19)
  - Palmer, Frederick to Dawson, Warrington, 1917 (Box 19)
  - Palmer, Helen to Dawson, Warrington, 1926 (Box 19)
  - Pape, Thomas Nelson to Morgan, Sarah, 1907 (Box 19)
  - Pape, Thomas Nelson to Dawson, Warrington, 1910-1913 (Box 19)
  - Pape, Thomas Nelson to Feakins, William, 1910 (Box 19)
  - Paris, W. Francklyn to Dawson, Warrington, 1931-1951 and undated (Box 19)
  - Parker, J. H. to Dawson, F. W., 1888 (Box 19)
  - Parker, John D. to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 19)
  - Parker, M. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889-1890 (Box 19)
  - Parker, William to [?], 1889 (Box 19)
  - Parsons, Frances to Dawson, Warrington, 1927 (Box 19)
  - Paterson, Robert to Dawson, Warrington, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Patterson, [N?] to [?], 1876 (Box 20)
  - Payne, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1900 (Box 20)
  - Pearson, Leon to Dawson, Warrington, 1947 (Box 20)
  - Peck, Sedley to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Peebles, S. to Dawson, F. W., 1889 (Box 20)
  - Pegram, J. to Morgan, Sarah, 1889 (Box 20)
  - Pegram, J. W. to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 20)
  - Pegram, R. M. to Dawson, F. W. or Morgan, Sarah, 1888-1889 (Box 20)
  - Pell, R. T. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Pell, S. H. P. to Dawson, Warrington, 1933-1934 (Box 20)
  - Pelletier, Fleury to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Pelly, Julian A. to Dawson, F. W., 1872 (Box 20)
  - Pelsencer, Paul to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Perato, Andre to Dawson, Warrington, 1920 (Box 20)
  - Perrier, A. to Dawson, Warrington, 1913 (Box 20)
  - Perry, William to Dawson, Warrington, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Peteckin, Julia to Bonham, Milledge, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Petty, Chas to Dawson, F. W., 1887 (Box 20)
  - Philip, F. J. to Dawson, Warrington, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Phillips, A. W. to Dawson, F. W., 1889 (Box 20)